we need to determine
what method we can use to find out if a
hash contains a specific value
and we're going to write a small program
to demonstrate this
so i've got our opposites hash up here
on line one in the editor
and this is going to be the calling hash
so let's take a look at the hash
documentation to see what method we
might use
there is a method called has value
and this method returns a boolean either
true or
false based on whether or not the
argument
is a value in the calling hash
so let's test this out
if our opposites hash
has the value negative
we'll output a message to the user
reflecting that
otherwise
we'll output nope so let's run our code
and
see if we get the expected result in
this case we're expecting to see the
output
got it
and we do
we can test this out with a value that
is not in the hash
and now we'll see the output nope
and that's what we see
the hash class has a lot of useful
methods so
be sure to take the time to review the
documentation